Stelios Diamantopoulos

≤ stdiamant95@gmail.com 📙 +306940165375 🏠 Haaksbergerstraat 576 Enschede

ABOUT ME

My name is Diamantopoulos Stelios i am 27 years old student coming from Greece . I live in the Netherlands for the last 3 years. Currently i am on my 3rd year of studies and recently finished my minor on Business and data analytics.

MOTO

 $1.01^{365} = 37.8$

 $0.99^{365} = 0.03$

"Daily consistent effort can lead to extraordinary results"

EDUCATION

Minor in Bussiness and Data Analytics

Saxion Univerity of Applied Science Berkeley University 2022 - 2023

B.Sc. in Electrical and Electronic Engineering

Saxion Univerity of Applied Science 2020 - 2024

pre-B.Sc. in Physics

University of -Thessaloniki 2013-2015

LINKS

Total SteliosDiamantopoulos

in Stelios Diamantopoulos

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

1.Sports

2.Martial Arts

3.Chess

4.Programming

EXPERIENCE

Intern - Rosen Group B.V.

2022-2023

- Working with supply chain data.
- **Cleaning Data**
- Fill missing column data using APIs
- · Create a Dashboard using streamlit

Teacher Assistant - Saxion University of Applied Science

2021-Present

I am a teacher assistant responsible for developing hardware setups for the assignmentsExperience working with cooling systems (Peltier Elements and thermos sensor devices) Experience working on LV applications (5-24V)

Electronic Engineer - Roboteam Twente

2021-2022

- Analyze and found solutions with electrical and fixture issues.
- · Managed the diagnosis and repair of electrical connections.
- Design a battery Level Indicator System

Teacher - Diastaseis

2016-2019

- · Teaching Mathematics and Physics to high school kids
- Grade Homework
- · Manage the study material

PROJECTS

Daily Ev Planner

• The 'Daily Ev Planner' is a software tool that allows users to manage the charging and discharging behavior of up to four electric vehicles (EVs) in a streamlined and user-friendly way. With features such as a plot tool, daily power exchange analysis, and battery view, users can easily visualize and analyze the performance of their EVs over time. The tool is designed to help users optimize system performance and efficiency by providing a comprehensive view of the charging and discharging behavior of their EVs.

Link: Daily EV Planning Tool

Generating SVG Defects for MEM Device Visual Inspection

2023

As part of my SSS project, I collaborated with a nanotechnology research team at Saxion University of applied science to develop a method for generating SVG defects over a model picture to improve the accuracy of visual inspections for MEM devices. By creating a diverse range of defects, we were able to train machine learning models more effectively and enhance the overall inspection process.

Self Driving Car 2021

· Using infrared sensors to make a car avoid obstacles and follow a white line.

Wireless fast Charging

2022

· Wireless power transfer for a small toy car.

Electronic Engineer at Roboteam Twente

2022

- · Analyzed and found solutions for problems with electronic and fixture issues.
- Diagnosed and repaired issues with electronic systems.
- Managed the diagnosis and repair of electronic circuits and wiring.
- · Design a battery-level indicator system

2021

Design my own chat-bot that responds to basic keywords.

CERTIFICATION

Matlab Basics 2021

· Fast program for Matlab basics offered by the MathWorks.

Data Analytics 2022

Program offered by Google on Coursera.

Custom Program On Advanced Bussiness inteligence

from Berkeley University

2022